Kha
[Music]
Hello everyone Namaste welcome back to my
second channel.  Yes guys this is my second
channel.  If you haven't subscribed,
why not?  So I forgot to introduce this vlog, so that's why I am doing it now.  It is going to be a
cute vlog
because first of all I will go to a
Korean school where the foreigner
children study there and
try to learn the Korean language and Korean culture [music], so
I will go there and inspire them a little
with my story.
I have been invited there because
I am also a foreigner in Korea and
I have been living in Korea for so many years
and I have completely integrated into the Korean society,
so I will
inspire those children a little that you know, like me,
they too can
live happily in Korea, can make friends and can have a
social life.  And
after that, my cameraman and I will go to
decorate the gel shoes
because you know, they are quite a
crazy trend.  I know that
this was a trend in India since you know 20 years ago.
But in Korea, there are less shoes
but there is no decoration on them which you can stick things on,
nor is there any trend of that.
So I had to try that one too, you know.
So [music] that's going to be the second part
of the blog.  So let's reduce this useless
nonsense.  And enjoy the
vogue.
So guys here we are and here is your young
name.  Hello [laughs]
let's go.  So guys, I'm here at the school now
and I'm going to
give you a tour of the school.  The entrance is here.  Here are the
slippers of all the students.
Usually in Korea you have to take off your shoes
and
wear these slippers.  Anyway the corridor remained in front of me.
So here it is.
[laughter]
Here's the girls' bedroom.  So this is how
the bedroom looks like.  Very Simple Guys
Our Fashion Today.  Tell us in the comments how the
fashion is.  I can't show you the boys' bathroom
because I can't go inside.
I think this is a you-know-what resting
area here.  So here the students sit
and can heat some food etc. in the microwave.  You
can drink water etc.   There were
also some plates here for eating food.  You
can take food from there, heat it and eat it here and if you want, if there are a lot of
books here, you can fill the books also.
What's inside the fridge, Guys?  IMT.  Wow
wow what is that?  There is nothing inside the fridge.
Oh here guys
11 students are coming.  1 two three four
five six.  That's so sweet.   The
Kam
Guys kids brought me some of this crack bread
type stuff.  So sweet.
The Kids Made It.
Guys, they have a baking class so they
made this.  Do you only introduce
yourself in the can you say your name again
please
or
let's go guys guys I am very tensed the
kids are already coming here and we have to
talk in Korean we need thermal care
[laughs]
let's try the cake
[music]
lemon
juice please
[laughs]
[music]
communim
[laughs]
so guys my lesson is over.  The lesson was only 30
minutes long.  So let's say
goodbye to school now and go back home.
Hey guys here are the steel glasses and
water dispenser.
Guys, this is the steel glass that is there in the school here.  I
remembered India.   Let's
go.  Guys, I will go home and tell you
how the students were.  He was very shy.
We
So Guys Yoojung also just went home
and I'm going home too.  So I was told
that 20 students were coming.
But in the end I think only seven or eight people had come.
And I was also told that they would
come from different countries.  But six were Chinese and
one was an Indonesian boy.  So what was
told to me, what I had expected was
quite different but still I had a lot of fun
but because all of them were Chinese, they did
not know Kurien very well
so they
could not talk to me properly, the kids always have fun with me,
talk to me, tease me
etc., they do it with the teachers, but
this student did
not know Kurien very well so that is why
we could not interact much,
I felt very bad about that
because I
wanted to have a little golgappa fight with them and bye-by there are
cute kids here.  It's
time for holidays now, so everyone is leaving school.
Dude, now all the moms, you know, are out here
walking with the kids and I
[laughs] will go home and do my musical work.
Dude, another purple, another purple package has arrived.   Let's
unbox it guys.
In another blog I showed this purple package.
But this is the other one and I'll
show you what's inside it right now.   It
is a homeware clothing brand and
I like its home clothes very much.  So that's why
I keep ordering You Know from here again and again.
Tank tops in other colors
and this sky blue tank top.  And
I like this top so much that I am
wearing another one underneath.  So the
pads that are already there are fitted inside it.
So you know you don't need to wear a separate bra.
And it makes your body
so tight and sexy.
That's why I like it so much.  So because of this
I also bought these different colors so that
I can match them with my other clothes.
You
can wear these normally over dresses or you
can wear them for workout.  Let's
open it.
Another bag inside the bag.
Oh my God.  A bag inside another bag, another
bag.  Tung Tung guys, I am ready to go out
and let me show you my fashion now.
I bought this bodysuit two
years ago and today I am wearing it for the first time.
And now let's go to the Korean traditional market
and make our slippers shiny and smooth.  Let's
go.  Let's take the metro from here now.  I have
n't shown you the full outfit, so I will show it to you now.
[Music]
Now I know why they're called jelly shoes
because quite, you know, they're made in a jelly type of thing.
Guys, by the way, they come in different colors.
[Music] White, this is black, and
red, but I thought the black would look
better.  I mean it
is not properly black but it is a slightly black
silver color.  People on the side are looking at the fo
and here someone is working on a laptop
[making music].
[Music]
Guys, I've just arrived at the underground
food court, the food market, so let's do
some food worship before decorating our slippers.
Then
Mani is
here at the coffee shop,
there's Korean food, we're preparing it.
Guys, my food is here.
This is one of my favorite Korean dishes.
Here, rice is placed under different clean vegetables.
This one is a pure vegetarian version.
But actually it is the fish oil that is present in kimchi.
So if you
can't eat fish, I think you can't eat kimchi and anything
made from kimchi.
Here is the spicy sauce to
add to it.
Here are all the side dishes along with the main dish.  And this is
black bean soup.   Let's add
a little spicy [MUSIC] sauce.
You guys also eat it.  [MUSIC]
I want to eat my food and it won't fall.  Impossible.   It doesn't
matter.  It works.
Before decorating the slippers, retouch the lipstick.
Its color is very beautiful
guys.   Of
all the lipsticks I have used, this one is the
longest lasting.  Mint
spray.
You will get all the materials required to make such jewellery
here.  Blue
colored stones.  You will find all kinds of colorful
dogs here.  But only one mong will be available.
Guys, look how many pearl
necklaces are there here.  Anyone who loves DIY can
take whatever materials are available here
and make their own jewellery.
What do these earrings look like to me?
[song voice]
I found the king and queen's jewelry.
Guys this is the shoulder patch.
Wow earrings
[singing voice]
Eat ice cream, guys.  Do you want a cup of
coffee?
Number one [laughs]
Raman.  Oh my god guys look what I found.
Guys this is the only Scris
store.  So many screeches.
I want to buy everything from here.
So many cute and bling bling
shiny things just like my toad.
Guys, look how many cute
jelly shoes there are here.  So now let us also decorate our shoes
beautifully.  We've
found this place to decorate our jelly shoes.
So let's grab some accessories from here.
Here all the girls are decorating their shoes beautifully.
But I don't understand what to
apply.  Here all the
girls are decorating their jewellery shoes.  There
is not even space to put your feet here.  So many people have come.  Guys
I have chosen the decoration and
I will show you after some time.
Ray Glass you made it another.
Guys, you must have seen this place
in many dramas because a lot of
people shoot here.  Talking about shooting,
someone's shooting is going on here too.
That cool guy is being shot there.
Please tell us in the comments which dramas have been shot on this wall.
Happy Birthday.  Guys look at it smile
it's
here too I got the
candle
[song voice]
[music]
Race
[song voice]
Guys I forgot to shoot the outro for this video.
So for today, I just hope
that you liked today's strange and cute vlog.
Please do tell us in the comments
which was your favorite part.
How did you like this blog and
what do you want to see next?  So thank you so much
for watching.  And by the way, my birthday is coming tomorrow, guys.  Bye bye.
Wow
no sir.
Can I take your picture?
How can you say this?   I
just vlogging.  Guys, that boy is going to
help me in the lesson I am going to take.
We drop this, in this much heat one should
wear such a T-shirt because it is
very very hot.